Shigeo, wait! Remain calm!
Look into my eyes!
I can tell these aren't real bodies!
They're dummies!
Some esper probably
put them here to fool you!
Come on, Dimple.
Does a psychic power like that really exist?
J-Just think about everything you've seen!
It's completely possible!
No, I know it's out there!
I found them.
Did he just learn how to do that?
That's gotta be our guy!
Dimple...
Thank you for stopping me.
We can't relax just yet.
We're going after them, aren't we?
Of course. I'm going to get all
three of them back right now.
Whoever did this won't get away with it.
No matter how far they run,
I will make them pay.
Obsession
Kill
Is there a point to setting the place on fire?
Makes it obvious that it's been dealt with.
What was that?
A meteor?
Who the hell is that?
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down, could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB. Can't you feel your own frustration?
You're a MOB. What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions on your sleeve and break it down.
What do you see once you go beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9!)
The mysterious percentage.
Cryin' my life, cryin' my psyche,
cryin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100.
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind? Right now...
Your life is your own.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
Mob Psycho
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Show Me What You've Got
~Band Together~
You're Hanazawa Teruki... aren't you?
Hanazawa? Oh, the guy that lives downsta—
Telekinetic Explosion!
I know you.
You're our target.
How the hell did you find out about us?
Well, whatever. You can die here.
Wow, looks like you're somewhat resilient.
Where'd you take my family?
This is great.
Let's see if you die from
electrocution first or I just bite it!
I'm not interested.
Use something other than electricity.
Wait, is that all you can do?
You're free to go.
Maybe you're the guy, then.
Show me your powers!
You've got a lousy attitude, kid.
If you want to see my powers
so badly, I'll show you!
They're fighting! Some old guy
and a middle school kid!
I have impregnable armor
made out of energy.
And I beat the crap out of my enemies.
That's my style.
Seriously...
Could you guys quit wasting my time?
Looks like you have a decent barrier.
Is that your power?!
Quit messing with me!
I want to see this power
that can create dummies!
Why did you attack my house?!
Someone call an ambulance and the police!
You've got the wrong idea...
We were on our way
to attack your house...
What?
Hey! Who said you could pass out?!
Hey!
Damn it...
I've contacted the upper echelon.
Now you're totally screw... ed.
This isn't good, Shigeo.
Seems there're more espers on the way.
We need to—
I haven't gotten any information yet, though.
If they have more friends coming,
I'll just have to ask them.
An umbrella?
Hey, you little shit. You in trouble?
Chill with the murderous vibe back there.
Former Claw
7th Division Member
Koyama
We're not trying to start
any trouble with you.
Right?
Former Claw
7th Division Member
Sakurai
If you have any questions,
I'll answer them for you, kid.
My family's wherever
you're taking me, aren't they?
Your family? No, they aren't.
Then I have no reason to go. Let me out.
Hang on! Your friends and master
are waiting there!
Reigen's there?
In that case, we need to hurry!
Yo, yo, wait, wait!
Don't be crazy!
Ugh, I'm going to throw up...
But we managed to shake anyone
who was tailing us.
We brought him.
Here's Kageyama Shigeo.
Long time no see, kid.
You haven't let yourself go, have you?
I know we used to be rivals,
but I look forward to working with you...
What the hell kind of gathering is this?
Mob, are you all right?
Master...
My home... My family...
Go on, but have a seat.
I'll actually explain everything
in Shigeo's place.
Currently explaining the situation
I see.
Dimple, I need to talk to you for a sec.
Sure.
Did you just panic and lie
about the dummies?
Kinda, but I do have reasons to believe it.
You must've really been panicking.
If Mob finds out you lied,
he's going to hate you forever.
Mob, I need to talk to you.
Are you going to tell him? Hang on a sec!
If he learns the truth...
Mob, your family...
I think they're safe, too.
Those guys were still on the way
to your house, right?
Someone must've known what
was going on and saved them.
They started the fire
and made them look dead
so they wouldn't be targeted anymore.
Isn't that great?
The moment he relaxed, he fell fast asleep.
Now it's your turn to talk.
What the hell brought you lot together?
Aren't these guys from Claw?!
Former Claw
7th Division Member
Tsuchiya
Us members of the 7th Division left Claw.
After being annihilated
by a group of middle school kids,
Former Claw
7th Division Member
Mukai
we realized just how foolish we were.
Mole
Former Claw 7th Division Member
Muraki
And now, we're all trying to start a new life.
Following Master Reigen's example,
we're trying to find a way to use
our powers for the good of society.
But the organization doesn't let traitors go.
We figured they'd come after us
sooner rather than later,
but this was a lot faster
than we anticipated.
Former Claw
7th Division Member
Terada
And they launched attacks on all of us
at the same time.
I'm impressed you survived that.
Who do you think we are?
We're former Scars.
Right, Tsucchi?
Yeah. But the real battle will begin
after the guys from HQ show up.
And then, we realized that
we're going to need a leader
if we want to stand a chance against HQ.
And so, they came to me.
You should probably shut up for a bit.
When we saw Master Reigen put
the TV and media people in their place,
we thought he was a genius.
He's able to see the bigger picture
and make things happen.
I seriously don't know about these guys...
You didn't get attacked?
My office was destroyed.
I just happened to be away
when it happened, thankfully.
Since I gained popularity
from my TV appearances,
I thought I could get some renovations done.
That's my office.
Spirits and Such Consultation Office
It's on fire...
But that's going to have to wait.
After that, these guys picked me up.
I was already exhausted from the marathon.
Talk about a crappy day.
I wonder if Teru-san's okay.
Oh, I got a message from him earlier.
He said he's fine.
They exchanged emails
When'd that happen?
This sucks...
What are you guys doing here?
We're trying to lay low after what
happened with the 7th Division.
Mitsuura-san prepared this hideout for us.
So many espers in one spot! I'm so moved!
Oh, him.
Teru-san!
Heya. Looks like the gang's all here.
You fools!
You'll never get a word out of me!
I'm a member of Cla—
Resistance is futile.
No one's been able to endure this torture.
Sorry! I'll talk!
The boss was going around the world
to scout powerful espers,
and he said he finally had
all the soldiers he needed!
I see... Espers from around the world, eh?
Don't tell me you fools still plan
to face us after hearing that...
What shall we do, Master Reigen?
Well, we can't just let this slide.
Let's report them to the police.
Isn't it amazing?
Claw Foreigner Squad
Joseph
Ordinary humans actually made all of this.
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to destroy it all.
Claw Foreigner Squad
Udo
That's why we came to this country, right?
Really?
I came here for the money.
Mob Psycho
Ladies and gentlemen,
Claw
I thank you all for gathering
on this memorable day.
I am the leader of Claw,
Suzuki Toichiro.
Claw Boss
Suzuki Toichiro (46)
Let's not waste any time.
We are about to declare war on the world.
After twenty years, I finally have
the funds and manpower that I need.
We will begin this revolution
with destruction.
Claw
We will destroy everything
that people built and hold dear.
Let us show the powerless that we exist!
Yeah!
World domination, eh?
Well, isn't that ambitious?
Are all the preparations complete?
Oh, I don't even need to prepare.
Claw
What are they doing?
Is that TV?
Now you're live on all channels.
Ultimate 5
Hatori
The ability to infiltrate and
control any kind of system
dealing with electronic devices or waves.
He doesn't actually understand
how it works, either.
He's good...
We are esper organization Claw.
We have taken over the airwaves
with our psychic powers.
This is a mere fraction of our true power.
Our powers are far superior
to modern weaponry.
Let me warn you that
it's not advisable to oppose us.
We will control the world with psychic powers
Another esper?
Too many espers lolololol
He's cray
and rule over all of the powerless.
What the hell is "Claw"?
Claw lolololol Edgy much? Lololololol
Apparently his brain stopped developing when he was a kid
Okay, well I'm gonna be a superhero then
Talk about lame
This shit again? So boring
I could probably take him in one punch
You may be a claw, but I'm just a toenail
Maki Maki
Oh, shit.
It's the end of the world lolololol
Yukki
lolololololol Read
Maki Maki
Edgelord lol
Who the hell is that?
Yukki
Hell if I know lolol Read
The first step in our mission
is to demolish this country.
A new world is about to begin.
Look forward to it.
Now you've done it, you piece of shit dad!
How dare you embarrass me like that again?!
Fukuda
Otsuki
Higashio
I'm the one who's going to defeat him!
You got that, Ritsu?!
Yeah.
All right! Let's go!
Hang on a sec.
What? You're still not on board?
What about my family's safety?
Oh, we have a set of eyes
on your parents from afar.
See?
We said that you, because you wanted
to do something nice for your parents,
Hot Springs Hotel Voucher
entered a hot springs hotel lottery and won,
and they totally fell for that lie.
You were really pushing it with that ad-lib.
That hot springs hotel doesn't have ties
to some shady organization, does it?
Streaming data
Don't worry. They offer both
traditional seafood and farm meat meals,
and they're happy to accommodate
any allergies, too.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Anyway, my brother's
still not answering his phone.
Your brother's not going to fight.
I could tell from his eyes.
He's not the type to blow up
without a real good reason.
I think I gave him a pretty good one, though.
What? Did you do something
after we left the house?
If you did something that
really pissed my brother off,
you're in big trouble.
Guess you've had a hard life, too.
600 people
I will now explain the plan
that the boss was talking about.
Claw 1st Division Leader
Tamaki
In Japan, the number of policemen
and military personnel who have guns
total roughly 600,000.
Meanwhile, our forces number around 600.
600 people
Each one will have to face
about a thousand in battle.
600,000
That shouldn't be a problem, right?
That's awesome!
That's our boss!
Who knew it'd be so easy?
This actually seems possible all of a sudden.
Can you even call that a plan?
It doesn't seem very likely to work.
This lot is hopeless.
What are you thinking, Joseph?
Probably the same as you guys.
According to his logic, if each
of us defeat about 120 people,
Foreigner Squad
People
we can destroy Claw.
We're going to start a mutiny?
That sounds fun.
Yes! I don't care what we do
as long as I get to break stuff!
First, we need to make an example
of the upper echelon.
What?
You're going to destroy this organization?
Claw 1st~6th Division Leaders
You're going to give up future glory
for the sake of money?
You vile creatures.
I'll take care of you myself.
Come at me all at once.
Teehee.
I'm gonna punch you now,
so I hope you can put up a barrier.
Claw, a dangerous esper organization, huh?
For something you've been plotting for
twenty years, it sure is full of holes.
Does an elephant that's about
to crush a thousand ants
have much to worry about?
I'm really starting to feel sorry for you.
You have no idea the Japanese government
already had their eyes on you,
nor who the person in front of you is.
So you were sent by the government?
Just me, yeah.
But I managed to get other guys on board.
This organization will implode
before this terrorist plot.
Claw is finished.
Hey, now.
You were lying to President Suzuki?
How could you do something so awful?!
White Noise!
It looks like it'd be hard
to move around in that.
Once it hardens, it's as hard as steel.
Anyone who gets caught in that is finished.
Miguel!
You said you felt sorry for me
a moment ago, didn't you?
But now, I feel sorry for you.
Could you not give me more work to do?
Ultimate 5
Minegishi
Well, this is pathetic.
These guys are supposed to
be in our upper echelon.
Look at them.
D-Damn it!
Shibata
Ultimate 5
I see you're the same type as me.
The loss of my division leaders
won't be enough for Claw to implode.
I've dubbed Claw's main force the Ultimate 5.
As long as the Ultimate 5 and I are around,
Claw is invincible.
I'm not done yet!
I can at least take you out here!
What?!
Well done.
I knew it'd be a waste to let you
continue being a shut-in.
Ultimate 5
Serizawa
Yes, sir! It's all thanks to you that
I was able to step back into society!
By the way, where's Shimazaki?
I haven't seen him.
I'm having him take care
of something else for me.
Damn them...
They're a bigger threat than we thought.
I had the best chefs prepare this meal!
Eat as much as you'd like!
I'm surprised HQ hasn't attacked yet.
I mean, we could strike first,
but considering our numbers...
Well, Kageyama-kun and I
are worth at least a thousand people.
Either way, nothing's starting
until the kid wakes up.
Stop eating all the roast beef, mohawk!
There's a limit of three per person!
Huh?
Apologize to Master Reigen, Koyama!
Lay the hell off!
They didn't see the message on TV.
So yes,
On Women's Empowerment
Lecturer: Prime Minister Yabe Hiroshi
by providing women more opportunities
to start their own business
and expanding the range of childcare welfare,
we can provide solutions to
sexual and authority harassment...
Nice to meet you, Prime Minister.
Ultimate 5
Shimazaki
I'm a member of Claw, who last night
declared they'd be taking over the world.
I've come to abduct you today.
Prime Minister, please come this way!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Hey, by the way, are you
broadcasting this on TV?
Damn it!
Shut up!
Don't move!
I sure hope we end up on breaking news.
Stop! Don't move!
Does he have a gun?
Freeze!
You missed.
The thing is, even though I can't see,
I can predict people's movements.
But even if I'm hit, I really
have nothing to worry about.
See?
Prime Minister, let me fill you in
on what my other special power is.
You see...
I can teleport.
Why are you kidnapping me?
What do you plan to do with me?
Nothing complicated. You're just a hostage.
Are you serious about
this world domination crap?
Oh, yes. Very much so.
And who might you be?
I saw the broadcast and rushed here,
and then I sensed you two in this park.
If you think everything in life
goes as planned,
let me teach you a lesson
by taking you down.
What a funny thing to say.
I guess you can try.
Telekinetic Explosion!
Air Whips!
He disappeared?
What? I was too careless!
Pyrokinesis!
I lost sight of him again.
Is this guy's power...
Over here.
Super speed movement?
In that case...
Multi-Layer Barrier!
My new technique where I
overlap multiple barriers...
While the enemy's trying to get through,
the others should get here.
Well, aren't you multi-talented.
That quick?
Thanks for entertaining me.
Hanazawa! Hey! Wake up!
Why the hell'd you run off on your own?!
I spilled a seed and lost sight of it
I'll find it using the color it's dyed in and watch it grow
It immediately returned to the palm of my hand
But it's still too light and too frail to reach for the skies
The world coldly drains away all the heat
The bright sunshine just isn't enough
The memories are closing off what lies ahead
Shake off their warmth and set off into the distance
If I let it wither, it'd be over just like that
But my hope just doesn't fade away
The main force of Claw,
the Ultimate 5, terrorize Seasoning City.
Meanwhile, the esper squad and
the boss's son, Sho, make their moves.
Mob, this is no time to be sleeping!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 II Episode 10:
"Collision ~Power Type~."
What do I recommend?
Collision
~Power Type~
The convenient option A
with the Blu-ray set!